- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Morgaine_p2v1
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_Morgaine_p2v1_01"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Morgaine_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Sun_p10
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Morgaine_p7
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Galahad_p3a
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Sun_p6v2
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Sun_p14
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Sun_p15
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Morgaine_p2v2
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc3
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Morgaine_p2v2
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc3
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Yash_p3
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: EdengroveV2Arc3
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_container
  NpcDestinationId: 0717_Warden
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99E_MSQ_11
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: ""
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_objective_title"
  Description: "@99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
